1. randomFirstName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomFirstName()
5. randomEmail = custom.RandomData.generateRandomEmail()
9. randomLastName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomLastName()
13. randomPhone = custom.RandomData.generateRandomPhone()
17. randomAddress = custom.RandomData.generateRandomAddress()
21. randomCode = custom.RandomData.generateRandomCode()
25. openBrowser(URL)
29. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
33. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
37. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-account"), "agungpriyadi")
41. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Password"), "Laskar123456")
45. click(findTestObject("Login/btn-sign in"))
49. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
53. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Address Management/Shipping Address/btn_My Address"), 4)
57. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Shipping Address/btn_My Address"))
61. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/radiobtn_Add New Address"))
65. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/field_First Name"), 10)
69. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/field_First Name"), 0)
73. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/field_First Name"), randomFirstName)
77. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/field_Last Name"), 0)
81. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/field_Last Name"), randomLastName)
85. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/field_Mobile Phone"), 0)
89. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/field_Mobile Phone"), randomPhone)
93. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/field_E-mail"), 0)
97. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/field_E-mail"), randomEmail)
101. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/field_Address"), 0)
105. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/field_Address"), randomAddress)
109. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/dropdown_Province"))
113. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/Dropdown Province/li_Banteay Meanchey Province"), 0)
117. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/Dropdown Province/li_Banteay Meanchey Province"))
121. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/dropdown_Select Province"))
125. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/Dropdown Select Province/li_Paoy Paet Municipality"), 0)
129. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/Dropdown Select Province/li_Paoy Paet Municipality"))
133. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/dropdown_Districts"))
137. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/Dropdown District/li_Sangkat Kandal"), 10)
141. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/Dropdown District/li_Sangkat Kandal"))
145. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/field_ZipPostal Code"), randomCode)
149. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Add New Address/button_Save"))
153. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Address Management/Shipping Address/lbl_Shipping Address"), 3)
157. takeScreenshot()
161. comment("Email      : " + randomEmail)
165. comment("First Name : " + randomFirstName)
169. comment("Last Name  : " + randomLastName)
173. comment("Phone      : " + randomPhone)
177. comment("Address    : " + randomAddress)
181. comment("Code    : " + randomCode)
185. closeBrowser()